<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Delphi Blog</title>
    <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Delphi Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/08/10/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/08/10/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Hello from the Delphi research group at Carnegie Mellon University!
We’re a group of faculty, students, and staff, based primarily out of CMU
together with strong collaborators from other universities and industry.
Our group was founded in 2012 to advance the theory and practice of epidemic
forecasting. Since March 2020, we have refocused efforts towards helping combat
the COVID-19 pandemic, by supporting informed decision-making at federal, state,
and local levels of government and in the healthcare sector. Until now, we’ve
been pretty “heads down” with our work, and slow to communicate what we’ve been
up to. But at last … Delphi finally has a blog! This first post serves as an
introduction of sorts. Future posts will dive deeper into our various projects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>In March 2020, the Delphi group at Carnegie Mellon University launched the COVIDcast project, a comprehensive effort to:
 build and maintain new data streams and indicators that reflect COVID-19 activity and burden, make that data available to researchers, journalists, and the public through a public API and packages for R and Python, build interactive maps and graphics to inform decision makers and the public, and develop forecasts of the future spread of the pandemic and healthcare demand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>