<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Delphi Blog</title>
    <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Delphi Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Open COVID-19 Data with the COVIDcast API</title>
      <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/10/05/sharing-open-covid-19-data-with-the-covidcast-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/10/05/sharing-open-covid-19-data-with-the-covidcast-api/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;One of our primary initiatives at the Delphi COVIDcast project
has been to curate a diverse set of COVID-related data streams,
and to make them freely available through our
&lt;a href=&#34;https://cmu-delphi.github.io/delphi-epidata/api/covidcast.html&#34;&gt;COVIDcast API&lt;/a&gt;.
These include both novel signals that we have collected and analyzed ourselves,
such as our symptom survey &lt;a href=&#34;https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/08/26/covid-19-symptom-surveys-through-facebook/&#34;&gt;distributed by Facebook&lt;/a&gt;
to its users, &lt;a href=&#34;https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/09/18/covid-19-symptom-surveys-through-google/&#34;&gt;Google’s symptom survey&lt;/a&gt; whose results are delivered to us,
the percentage of doctor’s visits due to COVID-like illness,
and results from Quidel’s antigen tests;
and also existing signals, such as the confirmed case counts
and deaths reported by USA Facts and Johns Hopkins University.
The COVIDcast API freely provides researchers and decision-makers
with the data they need to conduct their work, and
is conveniently accessible via easy-to-use &lt;a href=&#34;https://cmu-delphi.github.io/covidcast/covidcast-py/html/&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt;
and &lt;a href=&#34;https://cmu-delphi.github.io/covidcast/covidcastR/&#34;&gt;R&lt;/a&gt; packages.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Symptoms Surveys Improve COVID-19 Forecasts?</title>
      <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/09/21/can-symptoms-surveys-improve-covid-19-forecasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/09/21/can-symptoms-surveys-improve-covid-19-forecasts/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Building on our previous two posts (on our COVID-19 symptom surveys through
Facebook and Google)
this post offers a deeper dive into empirical analysis, examining whether the
% CLI-in-community indicators from our two surveys can be used to improve
the accuracy of short-term forecasts of county-level COVID-19 case rates.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Symptom Surveys through Google</title>
      <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/09/18/covid-19-symptom-surveys-through-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/09/18/covid-19-symptom-surveys-through-google/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Since April 2020, in addition to our massive daily survey advertised on
Facebook, we’ve been running (even-more-massive) surveys through Google to
track the spread of COVID-19 in the United States.
At its peak, our Google survey was taken by over 1.2 million people in a single
day, and over its first month in operation, averaged over 600,000 daily
respondents. In mid-May, we paused daily dissemination of this survey in order
to focus on our (longer, more complex) survey through Facebook,
but we plan to bring back the Google survey this fall.
This short post covers some key differences between our Google and Facebook
surveys, explains the backstory behind the “CLI-in-community” question
as it arose through our collaboration with Google,
and shares some of our thinking about next steps for the Google survey.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Symptom Surveys through Facebook</title>
      <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/08/26/covid-19-symptom-surveys-through-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/08/26/covid-19-symptom-surveys-through-facebook/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Since April 2020, in collaboration with Facebook,
partner universities, and public health officials,
we’ve been conducting a massive daily survey to monitor
the spread and impact of the COVID-19 pandemic in the United States.
Our survey, advertised by Facebook, is taken by about 74,000 people each day.
Respondents provide information about COVID-related
symptoms, contacts, risk factors, and demographics,
allowing us to examine county-level trends across the US.
We believe that this combination of &lt;em&gt;detail&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;scale&lt;/em&gt;
has never before been available in a public health emergency.
In this post, we’ll share some of our initial survey findings,
show you how to access the data, and highlight
some of the exciting new directions that we’re pursuing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/08/10/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/2020/08/10/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Hello from the Delphi research group at Carnegie Mellon University!
We’re a group of faculty, students, and staff, based primarily out of CMU
together with strong collaborators from other universities and industry.
Our group was founded in 2012 to advance the theory and practice of epidemic
forecasting. Since March 2020, we have refocused efforts towards helping combat
the COVID-19 pandemic, by supporting informed decision-making at federal, state,
and local levels of government and in the healthcare sector. Until now, we’ve
been pretty “heads down” with our work, and slow to communicate what we’ve been
up to. But at last … Delphi finally has a blog! This first post serves as an
introduction of sorts. Future posts will dive deeper into our various projects.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://delphi.cmu.edu/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>In March 2020, the Delphi group at Carnegie Mellon University launched the COVIDcast project, a comprehensive effort to:
 build and maintain new data streams and indicators that reflect COVID-19 activity and burden, make that data available to researchers, journalists, and the public through a public API and packages for R and Python, build interactive maps and graphics to inform decision makers and the public, and develop forecasts of the future spread of the pandemic and healthcare demand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>